Associated Industries of New York State / The Business Council of New York State; Records apap043
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Website of the Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1996 December 19 - 2017 March 27; 12; 364 captures
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 April 13
    Meta tag for keywords: New York State, Albany, business, government, advocacy, capital, capitol, economic growth, jobs, association, liability, membership, legislature, benefits, tort reform, regulatory, seminars, conferences, public policy, environment, health, transportation, government affairs, small business, energy, telecommunications, workers' compensation, consumer products, insurance, financial services, construction, taxation, osha, labor, human resources, unemployment compensation, business climate
    Meta tag for description: The Business Council of New York State is a statewide association of over 3,000 member businesses, working for a healthier business climate, economic growth, and jobs for New York State and its people.
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 April 30
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 May 13
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 May 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 June 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 July 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 September 18
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 December 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 December 19
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2009 February 7
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2010 January 11
    Meta tag for description: The Business Council of New York State is a statewide association of over 3,000 member businesses, working to create economic growth, good jobs and strong communities across New York State.
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2010 April 20
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2010 July 22
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2010 August 25
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2010 September 17
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2010 November 13
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2010 December 1
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2010 December 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 February 12
    Meta tag for description: The Business Council of New York State is a statewide association of over 2,500 member businesses, working to create economic growth, good jobs and strong communities across New York State.
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 February 22
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 February 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 April 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 April 21
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 May 4
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 May 18
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 May 23
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 June 25
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 July 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 July 18
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 August 10
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 August 31
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 September 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 September 14
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 September 28
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 October 8
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 November 8
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2011 December 9
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2012 January 17
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2012 February 4
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2012 May 9
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2012 May 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2012 August 15
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2012 September 9
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2012 September 20
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2012 October 29
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 January 21
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 March 25
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 April 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 April 22
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 April 30
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 May 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 May 14
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 May 24
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 May 31
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 June 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 November 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2013 December 4
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 February 20
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 March 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 April 9
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 May 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 July 1
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 September 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 October 4
  - not present, 2014 November 1
    Meta tag for description: The Business Council of New York State, Inc. is a statewide association of over 2,400 private sector employers, working to create economic growth, good jobs and strong communities across New York State.
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 December 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2014 December 19
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 February 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 February 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 February 22
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 March 18
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 July 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 July 25
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 August 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 September 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2015 December 24
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 January 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 January 19
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 January 31
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 February 9
    crawl: 195208
    This item had no crawl rules.
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2016-02-09T14:14:51Z
    original_start_date: 2016-02-09T14:14:51Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2016-02-09T17:44:06Z
    end_date: 2016-02-09T17:35:21Z
    elapsed_ms: 12019289
    Crawl Types
    type: TEST_SAVED
    recurrence_type: NONE
    pdfs_only: False
    test: True
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 86400
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED
    discovered_count: 7343
    novel_count: 7204
    duplicate_count: 139
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 0
    downloaded_count: 7343
    download_failures: 4
    warc_revisit_count: 139
    warc_url_count: 7341
    total_data_in_kbs: 527989
    duplicate_bytes: 2738415
    warc_compressed_bytes: 410536304
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.61
    kb_rate: 43.0
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 February 9
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 March 3
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 March 15
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 March 20
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 March 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 April 14
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 April 23
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 May 27
    crawl: 214993
    start_date: 2016-05-27T14:57:42Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-27T14:57:42Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-27T18:32:30Z
    end_date: 2016-05-27T18:24:05Z
    elapsed_ms: 12368672
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    test: False
    time_limit: 259200
    discovered_count: 7851
    novel_count: 5476
    duplicate_count: 2375
    downloaded_count: 7851
    warc_revisit_count: 2375
    warc_url_count: 7849
    total_data_in_kbs: 1615412
    duplicate_bytes: 418765373
    warc_compressed_bytes: 138818188
    doc_rate: 0.63
    kb_rate: 130.0
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 May 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 June 27
    crawl: 222067
    start_date: 2016-06-27T14:57:46Z
    original_start_date: 2016-06-27T14:57:46Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-27T18:53:14Z
    end_date: 2016-06-27T18:31:17Z
    elapsed_ms: 12790822
    discovered_count: 7782
    novel_count: 5390
    duplicate_count: 2392
    downloaded_count: 7782
    warc_revisit_count: 2392
    warc_url_count: 7780
    total_data_in_kbs: 1585692
    duplicate_bytes: 1480976138
    warc_compressed_bytes: 55208888
    kb_rate: 123.0
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 June 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 July 27
    crawl: 227401
    start_date: 2016-07-27T14:57:53Z
    original_start_date: 2016-07-27T14:57:53Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-07-27T18:36:27Z
    end_date: 2016-07-27T18:28:08Z
    elapsed_ms: 12597544
    discovered_count: 7831
    novel_count: 5360
    duplicate_count: 2471
    downloaded_count: 7831
    warc_revisit_count: 2471
    warc_url_count: 7829
    total_data_in_kbs: 1612606
    duplicate_bytes: 1512466858
    warc_compressed_bytes: 52411117
    doc_rate: 0.62
    kb_rate: 128.0
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 July 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 August 27
    crawl: 232944
    start_date: 2016-08-27T14:57:48Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-27T14:57:48Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-27T18:50:00Z
    end_date: 2016-08-27T18:41:23Z
    elapsed_ms: 13397408
    discovered_count: 7712
    novel_count: 5405
    duplicate_count: 2307
    downloaded_count: 7712
    warc_revisit_count: 2307
    warc_url_count: 7710
    total_data_in_kbs: 1598930
    duplicate_bytes: 1485599342
    warc_compressed_bytes: 63198613
    doc_rate: 0.58
    kb_rate: 119.0
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 August 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 September 13
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 September 27
    crawl: 238672
    start_date: 2016-09-27T14:58:00Z
    original_start_date: 2016-09-27T14:58:00Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-09-27T19:26:49Z
    end_date: 2016-09-27T18:42:32Z
    elapsed_ms: 13463826
    discovered_count: 7823
    novel_count: 5420
    duplicate_count: 2403
    downloaded_count: 7823
    warc_revisit_count: 2403
    warc_url_count: 7821
    total_data_in_kbs: 1604545
    duplicate_bytes: 1496513336
    warc_compressed_bytes: 57650206
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 September 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 October 10
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 October 26
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 October 27
    crawl: 245129
    start_date: 2016-10-27T14:57:53Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-27T14:57:53Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-27T18:37:08Z
    end_date: 2016-10-27T18:26:38Z
    elapsed_ms: 12519004
    discovered_count: 7797
    novel_count: 5415
    duplicate_count: 2382
    downloaded_count: 7797
    warc_revisit_count: 2382
    warc_url_count: 7795
    total_data_in_kbs: 943232
    duplicate_bytes: 573852893
    warc_compressed_bytes: 302615928
    kb_rate: 75.0
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 October 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 November 22
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 November 27
    crawl: 251324
    start_date: 2016-11-27T14:57:45Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-27T14:57:45Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-27T18:52:02Z
    end_date: 2016-11-27T18:37:51Z
    elapsed_ms: 13195331
    discovered_count: 7850
    novel_count: 5436
    duplicate_count: 2414
    downloaded_count: 7850
    warc_revisit_count: 2414
    warc_url_count: 7848
    total_data_in_kbs: 1602991
    duplicate_bytes: 1489112140
    warc_compressed_bytes: 62067866
    doc_rate: 0.59
    kb_rate: 121.0
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 November 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 December 27
    crawl: 256975
    start_date: 2016-12-27T14:57:58Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-27T14:57:58Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-27T18:46:17Z
    end_date: 2016-12-27T18:32:45Z
    elapsed_ms: 12862989
    discovered_count: 7858
    novel_count: 5380
    duplicate_count: 2478
    downloaded_count: 7858
    warc_revisit_count: 2478
    warc_url_count: 7856
    total_data_in_kbs: 1603107
    duplicate_bytes: 1497110873
    warc_compressed_bytes: 55145960
    kb_rate: 124.0
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2016 December 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2017 January 26
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2017 January 27
    crawl: 263667
    start_date: 2017-01-27T14:57:52Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-27T14:57:52Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-27T18:40:33Z
    end_date: 2017-01-27T18:30:48Z
    elapsed_ms: 12767282
    discovered_count: 7759
    novel_count: 5406
    duplicate_count: 2353
    downloaded_count: 7759
    warc_revisit_count: 2353
    warc_url_count: 7757
    total_data_in_kbs: 1594038
    duplicate_bytes: 1478129110
    warc_compressed_bytes: 64137052
  - WARC file for The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2017 January 27
  - Down for Maintenance - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2017 February 27
    crawl: 269571
    start_date: 2017-02-27T14:57:52Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-27T14:57:52Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-27T15:08:33Z
    end_date: 2017-02-27T14:58:30Z
    elapsed_ms: 21136
    discovered_count: 34
    novel_count: 11
    duplicate_count: 23
    downloaded_count: 34
    download_failures: 0
    warc_revisit_count: 23
    warc_url_count: 32
    total_data_in_kbs: 188
    duplicate_bytes: 159695
    warc_compressed_bytes: 55524
    doc_rate: 1.61
    kb_rate: 8.0
  - WARC file for Down for Maintenance - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2017 February 27
  - Internet Archive Wayback Machine, 2017 March 27
    crawl: 286723
    start_date: 2017-03-27T14:57:45Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-27T14:57:45Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-27T18:11:33Z
    end_date: 2017-03-27T18:01:52Z
    elapsed_ms: 11041898
    novel_count: 5492
    duplicate_count: 2290
    warc_revisit_count: 2290
    total_data_in_kbs: 1580960
    duplicate_bytes: 1457376378
    warc_compressed_bytes: 79173664
    doc_rate: 0.7
    kb_rate: 143.0
  - WARC file for Internet Archive Wayback Machine, 2017 March 27